<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mars Application</string>
    <string name="mars_mission">The Mars 2020 rover mission is
        part of NASAs Mars Exploration Program, a long-term effort
        of robotic exploration of the Red Planet. The Mars 2020
        mission addresses high-priority science goals for Mars
        exploration, including key questions about the potential for life on Mars.
        The mission takes the next step by not only seeking signs of habitable conditions
        on Mars in the ancient past, but also searching for signs of past microbial life itself.
        The Mars 2020 rover introduces a drill that can collect core samples of the most
        promising rocks and soils and set them aside in a "cache" on the surface of
        Mars. The mission also provides opportunities to gather knowledge and
        demonstrate technologies that address the challenges of future human
        expeditions to Mars. These include testing a method for producing oxygen from
        the Martian atmosphere, identifying other resources (such as subsurface water),
        improving landing techniques, and characterizing weather, dust, and other
        potential environmental conditions that could affect future astronauts
        living and working on Mars.</string>

    <string name="mars_curiosity">Part of NASAs Mars Science Laboratory mission,
        Curiosity is the largest and most capable rover ever sent to Mars.
        Early in its mission, Curiositys scientific tools found chemical
        and mineral evidence of past habitable environments on Mars.
        It continues to explore the rock record from a
        time when Mars could have been home to microbial life.</string>

    <string name="mars_opportunity">Opportunity was the second of the two
        rovers launched in 2003to land on Mars and begin traversing the
        Red Planet in search ofsigns of past life. Opportunity has made a number
        of discoveries about the Red Planet including dramatic evidence that long ago
        at least one area of Mars stayed wet for an extended period and that
        conditions could have been suitable for sustaining microbial life.</string>

    <string name="mars_spirit">ABOUT THE MISSION
One of two rovers launched in 2003 to explore Mars and search for signs of past life,
        Spirit far outlasted her planned 90-day mission. In May 2009, the
        rover became embedded in soft soil at a site called "Troy" with only
        five working wheels to aid in the rescue effort. After months of
        testing and carefully planned maneuvers, NASA ended efforts to free
        the rover and eventually ended the mission on May 25, 2011.</string>


    <string name="opportunity">Opportunity</string>
    <string name="curiosity">Curiosity</string>
    <string name="spirit">Spirit</string>

    <string name="rover_select_title">Key Facts About Rover</string>

    <string name="FHAZ">Front Hazard Avoidance Camera</string>
    <string name="RHAZ">Rear Hazard Avoidance Camera</string>
    <string name="MAST">Mast Camera</string>
    <string name="CHEMCAM">Chemistry and Camera Complex</string>
    <string name="MAHLI">Mars Hand Lens Imager</string>
    <string name="MARDI">Mars Descent Imager</string>
    <string name="NAVCAM">Navigation Camera</string>
    <string name="PANCAM">Panoramic Camera</string>
    <string name="MINITES">Mini Thermal Emission Spectrometer</string>

    <string name="Search">Search Image</string>

</resources>
